You? Working?
Yeah. Jun's birthday's coming up, you know?
I want to give him a present,
but I don't have any money.
Do you know what kinds of jobs high
school kids are allowed to do?
O-Of course I do!
The ones where you say, like,
"Welcome!" and stuff...
They call it the service industry, right?
Even if you don't like how your boss or
the customers look, you can't punch them.
How about I punch you first?
I guess I have no choice.
Huh?
The idea of sending you off
to work alone worries me,
so I'll work with you.
Really?!
Thanks! That makes me feel a lot better!
Let me in on it, too.
Oh, you wanna work part-time, too?
I do!
Wait, what? You wanna work part-time?
Then why don't all of you...
work at my place?
When I throw a jab or a straight,
it always lands
But when I'm aiming for your heart,
I miss every time
Parallel, zigzagging, awkward, incoherent
When you look my way and move closer to me
I know it doesn't mean the same thing for you
But I wish we could stay like this forever
My changing feelings are driving me crazy
The moment you turn to face me,
take that! Telepathy
If only we could feel the same thing
I want to kick this pesky subtlety away
I want to know everything,
I want to know everything
I can't fool you forever
I can't keep this hidden
I want to shout out my secret, AHHH
Take that! Telepathy
Te-te-te-telepathy
Telepathy
My First Part-Time Job
"My First Part-Time Job."
God Ramen Tatsumi
Welcome, welcome! This is
my family's restaurant!
Tatsumi's told me about you three.
God Ramen Tatsumi
I'm his dad, Tatsuro.
Glad to have you on board.
H-Hello!
Thank you for letting us work here.
Thanks!
Boy, you have no idea how much
I appreciate you doing this.
My wife and I were running
this restaurant on our own,
but just recently, she...
went home to visit her family!
Come back to me, Kiyomi!
Don't mind him. This happens all the time.
Hey...
Do I really have to work in this?
Yay! It's cute!
I'm so glad I got those in case
we ever got any female help!
This was your idea?!
These don't look much like
ramen shop uniforms!
In that case, I'm okay with not
being a ramen shop anymore.
Come on, boss!
That's the uniform.
What other choice is there?
God Ramen Tatsumi
Just shut up and wear it.
So why aren't you wearing it?!
God Ramen Tatsumi
Okay, we're open!
We got a customer! Welcome!
Uh... Wel...co...
Welcome.
Will this seat at the counter be all right?
Uh, sure.
Hi there. Whatcha wanna eat?
Huh? Uh...
What would you recommend?
Recommend?
Yeah. What do you think tastes the best?
Oh! Well, I like cake.
Huh? You have that here?
I'm afraid not.
God Ramen Tatsumi
5 Toppings FREE
You're clearly useless at
dealing with customers,
God Ramen Tatsumi
5 Toppings FREE
so at least be a panda.
Okay.
Hey, Tomo-chan...
What noise do pandas make?
Huh? They're like bears,
so... I guess they roar?
Roar!
Thank you for your patronage.
Come again!
When we're working side by side like this,
it almost feels like you
married into my family!
I'm sorry. I didn't quite catch that.
Could you say it again?
I said it feels like you
married into my family.
One more time.
It... It feels like you...
Can you still say that?
S-Sorry.
Miso ramen with a side of gyoza, please.
You got it!
Welco—
Tomo?!
Hey, Kubojun! Good to see you again!
Hey, Tanabe... What's going on here?
There was one outside, too.
Well, actually...
Welcome.
Allow me to show you to your seat.
You're... Gundo, right?
You would forget the face
of a childhood friend?
Forgive my rudeness, sir,
but are you a chicken or something?
Right this way. Your seat is over here.
Yep, that's Gundo.
Hey, Tanabe! What did you mean by "again"?
Does he come here that often?!
Y-Yeah, once a week or so.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
I'll throttle you!
Uh, sorry...
Well? What do you think of
Tomo in her waitress uniform?
I was surprised, but...
I mean... I guess it's nice.
"I guess it's nice"?
What do you think that means?
I think that means it's fine.
Here's your char siu ramen.
Thanks...
Go on and laugh if you want.
Huh?
I mean, I look ridiculous in this, don't I?
No, I... don't think it looks bad at all.
"Not bad"? What do you think that means?
I think that means it's fine.
Great meal.
Th-Thank you very much. Please come again.
This feels kinda weird, huh?
How long are you gonna keep working here?
Huh? Just until the end of the long weekend.
Okay, I'll come back tomorrow,
then. Keep it up.
I brought some customers.
Thank you for waiting.
No problem!
God Ramen Tatsumi
3 Days Later
Great work, all of you.
These have been a fun few days.
And here's your pay.
Boss... Thanks for everything!
Yay! Money!
Isn't this more than you promised us?
Since you all worked so hard,
I added a bit extra.
I think that was to be expected,
given that we produced results.
R-Right...
Did she squeeze it out of him?
Will the shop be okay without us?
Don't worry! It's about time for Mom to
make her periodic trip back here, anyway.
If I'm being honest, I'd love to
have you keep working here...
We'd be glad to come back and
help you out occasionally.
What? Really?!
There aren't many employers that
give workers so much freedom.
I wanna come back again, too!
I feel like I'm making a
deal with the devil.
Jun?
Hey.
You waited to meet me
after work again today?
Well, Tomo, see you at school.
Yep!
I'll walk home with Misuzu-chan.
Not so close.
You actually came to the restaurant
every day of our break.
You that bored?
I went because you were there.
I figured if you went on some wild rampage,
they'd need someone around
who could stop you.
Huh?! What do you think I am, exactly?!
Besides...
I've eaten their ramen tons of times,
but for some reason, it seemed to taste
better when you brought it to me.
So... you know...
Good job.
Th-Thanks.
I can really have this?!
Yep. It's your birthday present.
It's just a cheap one, though.
That's totally fine! It's great!
Incidentally, I wear the same one.
That doesn't bother you, does it?
Of course it doesn't bother me!
As long as it's you, I wouldn't
mind matching from head to toe!
H-Head to toe?!
I mean, that'd be cool, right?
Like we're a team!
Oh... Right, a team.
It hasn't been like this in so long.
I thought he'd changed recently,
but I guess Jun is still Jun.
I bought cake, too.
Wanna have a birthday party at your place?
My mom's... gonna be home late tonight.
Huh? Oh...
S-So if we're having a party,
can it be at your place?
I'm sure Akemi-san will be there.
Y-Yeah, that makes sense.
Maybe something really is different!
The Abandoned Cinderella
"The Abandoned Cinderella."
Misuzu...
What can I do to make Jun see me as a girl?
Haven't heard that in a while.
Things have been going
great lately, thanks to you!
I figure if I'm gonna push, now's the time!
Got any ideas that'll work quick?
Let him touch your chest?
Huh?
Wh-What the hell are you saying?!
The chest would be too much,
but sharing bodily contact is the
quickest way to move forward.
Sharing contact? But it's
not that easy to just...
Don't worry. I have a plan.
You do?
Yes. All you have to do is stand facing him.
Then I'll...
push him into you from behind.
What's with you today?
A regular push probably won't
be enough to even budge him,
so I'll push him down from here.
That's dangerous!
It's fine as long as you catch him.
That's not the issue here!
Ah, I get it.
You don't feel confident
that you could catch him.
Huh?
Who do you think I am?
I can catch a Jun or two, no problem!
Perfect. I changed the subject to muscles.
What're you doing here?
Hey, Tomo. What are you doing down there?
I'm ready anytime.
Bring it on!
Huh? Bring what on? What are you—
Is this girl...
trying to flat-out kill me now?!
Now, go. And put on a pathetic
display of confusion.
Just like before.
Hell yeah!
Bring it!
Huh?! He dodged me?!
Oh, it's Jun-kun.
Ooh. Bad Jun-kun.
Sorry! It wasn't on purpose!
Let me make it up to you!
If there's anything I can do, name it!
Aw, that's okay, really.
It is not okay! Treat yourself better!
In various ways!
Then...
Tomo, do it! Don't hold back!
Are you sure? None of this was your fault.
I'm sure! Do it!
More!
What I did today was way
over the line, even for me.
What in the world am I...
Misuzu-cha—
Is this divine retribution?
Ow...
You okay, Misuzu-chan?
Must be my lucky day, to have
Misuzu-chan fall on me...
I'm sorry, Tanabe-kun.
You're not hurt, are you?
Huh?
Wh-Wh-What's wrong with you, Misuzu-chan?!
Not only did you apologize,
but you're showing concern for me?!
Oh, no! Did you hit your head?!
I'm fine.
You saved me by cushioning my fall.
Should I do something to thank you?
That's not necessary!
You don't need to hold back.
Right now... I just feel
a pressing need to atone.
I don't quite get it, but...
A chance like this doesn't come every day!
What should I ask her to do, though?
How far can I go? Should I just
push as far as I dare? Or...
Oh, crap!
I thought about it too long!
She's almost back to her usual self!
I-I'd really like to... swap contact info!
Okay, then. I got off a lot
easier than I expected.
Damn it! I could've gotten more?!
Hey, Misuzu-chan.
What was that all about earlier?
I finally realized something.
It seems I don't want Tomo and
Junichiro to get together.
Huh?
All this time, all I've
done is get in their way.
Are you sure about that?
I don't think you're as
bad as you think you are.
Carol...
Misuzu-chan...
Get off me.
Even now, I still can't get away with it?
Misuzu's pretty late.
Did she oversleep?
She said she was staying home sick today.
I didn't know about that.
How did you find out?
I got a message from her.
Why'd she only tell you?
Don't get all smug!
We'll start homeroom now.
Today, we'll assign parts for our production
of Cinderella at the cultural festival.
Cultural Festival
"Cinderella"
• Cinderella
• Prince
• Stepmother
• Stepsister 1
• Stepsister 2
• Fairy Godmother
Who should play the part of Cinderella?
3 Days Later
I've never taken this many days off before.
I just can't bring myself to face Tomo.
There are many things I want to say,
but first, why did you come to the window?
I would've felt bad making you
go downstairs when you're sick.
That's a favor I never asked for.
C'mon, don't play tough.
I bought all kinds of sweet
stuff for ya! Want 'em?
I do not.
I've got those things that
cool your forehead down, too!
No, thanks.
Okay.
What is all this?
You're not acting like yourself.
Well, lately it seems like she's the
only one you wanna be friends with.
It's great that you're getting
along so well with Carol...
but you've been avoiding me, haven't you?
I think my cold just came back.
I'm going to sleep.
Hey! No fair!
Jeez...
"Cinderella"
Here. It's the script for
our cultural festival play.
Read up.
If you don't like me anymore,
I can't help that.
But if that's not the case,
you're probably just overthinking things.
Overthinking... Yeah, maybe to her.
No matter how horrible
I made myself out to be,
I'm sure she'd just smile and
forgive me like it was nothing.
But that's exactly why I...
What the hell is this about
me being Cinderella?!
C-Calm down, Misuzu!
I'm a girl, and they're
making me play the prince!
The whole class decided together.
Who gave my name first?!
Oh...
I know!
Misuzu-chan should be Cinderella!
That was me.
You're gonna rip her cheeks off!
Hey.
So you finally showed up, Cinderella.
What?
You think you're in any
place to make fun of me?!
You're playing a tree!
Yeah, yeah! You're a tree!
Quit making things even more
complicated when you're a tree!
Cinderella
Act 1
"Cinderella's House"
We'll begin the play practice now.
Everyone with a part, come up front.
"Cinderella"
Act 1
"Cinderella's House"
Cinderella, hurry up and prepare our dinner!
Hey, Cinderella! You'd better have
finished the laundry I told you to do!
Cinderella, have you
finished cleaning my room?
Clean your own damn room.
Sh-She's scary!
Mother!
Don't worry. It's all right.
Hey, calm down! It's just play practice!
Why is she playing the stepmother?
I can't concentrate in here.
Let's practice our lines somewhere else.
Uh, sure.
Greetings, my prince.
Wh-What a beautiful l-lady you are!
W-Would you d-dance with—
Literally no one is this awkward.
Well, I mean, I've never acted before!
How do I even do it?
In your case, you could probably
just talk the way you normally do.
What a beautiful lady you are.
Would you dance with me?
See? That's no good at all!
It's perfect, you lady-killer.
You're so lucky. You and
Carol make great princesses.
Hardly. This isn't my kind of thing, either.
I wouldn't say I wish I could
be a princess or anything,
but if I'm the type to play a prince,
no one's ever gonna see me as a girl.
I don't see why there couldn't
be princesses like you.
Huh?
Having you play Cinderella might
be a bit too much to ask, but...
You could be a bandit princess.
How about I rob you blind?
Well, we should be heading back.
Right.
Tomo says she wants to
go out with Junichiro,
but she's convinced herself that
she's not worthy of that right now.
And it's all because...
Then why not act more like a girl?
I put that curse on Tomo.
Now I have to undo it.
There's no one else who can.
Tomo-chan, you look so handsome!
Really? This is kinda embarrassing...
Th-The binder busted loose!
We need to wrap her tighter!
Wow...
She's a princess...
Aizawa-san, you've got a knack for this!
R-Really?
That dress looks great on you, Olston-san.
Thanks!
Hey, can I call you "Carol-chan"?
Sure!
Oh! Then I will, too!
Everyone else is moving forward,
yet only I'm still...
Something bothering you?
Since it's you, I'm guessing it's about Tomo?
Mind your own business.
I bet you're only thinking of roundabout
ways to deal with it, right?
Why don't you try facing
her head-on for once?
Damn it! I can't get up!
You're the last person
I want to hear that from.
All the prep's on track. Now we just
wait for the festival to start.
You're so laid-back about this.
I've got nothing but stress.
If you've got nothing to do,
help me practice my lines.
No way. Cinderella's basically
the only character you talk to.
Jun as... Cinderella?
Wh-What's wrong with that?
Just do it! It doesn't bother me!
Yeah, it might not bother you, but...
Wait! Please, wait!
I want to know more about you!
I-I'm very sorry, Your Highness.
I have to g-g-go now.
F-Farewell.
Please don't go!
Look, can we please stop now?
This is kinda fun!
Help me out a little more!
Huh?!
Please don't go, Cinderella!
I-I can't stay!
Please remove your hand, Your Highness!
(This suspicious behavior is...)
Hey, you know, I'm all mixed up
It's too complicated, I'm freaking out
I want to look cute to you
(crazy, crazy, drive me crazy, and that's…)
So I'm plotting, bargaining,
sly, and stubborn
Dizzying love
Just tell him to look at you
And watch him stiffen up even more,
because you're both so awkward
What? Even if we're alike in that way
It doesn't make me happy, 'cause it
means our love is going nowhere
Cloudy heart, swirling emotions—
I sense rain coming
So I partly open my umbrella,
then sneakily scoot closer to you
Please notice the curl of my
eyelashes as I keep blinking
And don't say I'm acting weird
All this plotting and bargaining
is my sly plan to look cute to you
Try to solve the riddle of
this soft, dizzying love
(Buzzing, fidgeting)
Listen, I might be a bit
tangled in my own web now
But once you unravel the mystery,
you'll see pure lo-love